tinnitusremedy.com 2016-06-29

# TinnitusRemedy.com - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

TinnitusRemedy.com takes your privacy seriously, and has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to online privacy. Keep reading to learn more about our information gathering and dissemination practices, and our use of personally identifiable information. 

IP Addresses 

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our site or web server, and for the general administration of our website. Your IP address, should you decide to register and/or create a TinnitusRemedy.com account, is also used to help prevent you from creating duplicate accounts. 

Cookies 

Upon your first visit to this web site, a "cookie" is sent to your computer. A cookie is a tiny file that identifies you as a unique user. It stores personal preferences and user data, however, in no way does this tell us who you are. TinnitusRemedy.com has two primary uses for its cookies. 

First, we use cookies to track special offers and promotions that may be presented to you as you navigate our website. This is done so that you are not presented with the same special offers and/or promotions over and over, or after you have indicated you are not interested. 

While both of these activities depend on the use of a "cookie," visitors to this site always have the option of disabling cookies in their web browser. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. 

Information Gathering 

This web site collects online contact information in various ways, including inquiry forms and registration forms. The information collected may be used to send or call the user with information about our company, 

or to get in touch with the user when necessary. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings/calls; see the opt-out/modify section below. 

Links to Other Sites 

TinnitusRemedy.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame of content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. 

Also, via our site you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. TinnitusRemedy.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party. 

Please be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of TinnitusRemedy.com and this policy. 

Children Under 13 

TinnitusRemedy.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe TinnitusRemedy.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us. 

Security 

This web site has security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse and/or alteration of the information that you provide. Furthermore, we have taken every precaution technically possible to prevent any unauthorized access to the contents of this web server. 

Opt-Out/Modify 

TinnitusRemedy.com provides every user with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future communications from us, change and modify information previously provided, or remove their information from our databases altogether. 

1\. Email: s u p p o r t ^at^ TinnitusRemedy.com 

Contacting TinnitusRemedy.com 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this web site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us via one of the methods above. 

Policy Changes 

TinnitusRemedy.com reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time.
